Curriculum Vitae

Brandon Swatek

Residence: Piastowska 47/652

30-067 Kraków

Email address: <u>bswatekpost@gmail.com</u>

Phone number: (+48) 793 315 661



About me

I am learning about Computer Science related subjects for a third year now. Currently, I am a second year undergraduate at Jagiellonian University's FAIS faculty. I would love to learn practical skills and gain some actual working experience in programming. I hope to find satisfaction and fulfillment in my work. I will gladly start off as an Intern in your company.

Experience

10.2019 - current Mex Bistro sp. z o.o.

Bartender

Customer service at the bar.

07.2019 - 08.2019 Winner Recruitment

Warehouse employee

Job in the post warehouse on varied appointments in the Great Britain

10.2017 – 04.2018 Amrest sp. z o.o.

Restaurant employee – waiter, bartender, kitchen employee

Work at Pizza Hut restaurant including client service as a waiter, and

being member of a team as a bartender and an kitchen employee.

04.2017 - 07.2017

Tempo-Team

Production line / order picker employee

Job on production line for Giant and as order picker for Albert Heijn in the Netherlands.

Education

2018 - current Computer Science at Jagiellonian University's Faculty of Physics,

Astronomy and Applied Computer Science in Cracow

2013 - 2016 VI LO im. Juliusza Słowackiego in Kielce

Abilities

Basic knowledge of C, C++, Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

- Basic knowledge of algorithms and data structures
- Basic knowledge of Linux system and Microsoft's Office package
- Finished academic maths courses
- Native polish speaker, advanced english language skill
- Teamwork, problem solving, creativity, willingness to learn, openness, tranquility

Additional information

- My profile on github.com : https://github.com/ATallWhiteFountain
- My profile on linkedin.com : <u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/brandon-swatek-2487b3187</u>
- My personal site: https://atallwhitefountain.github.io/Personal-site/main.html

Interests

IT world, travelling, music, history, ethics, cooking

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochronie danych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).